Finding Aid for the Donald Kalish Papers LSC.0578
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Concerned Faculty material (Fall), 1986 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Clippings on Mary Brent Wehrli and Ramsey Clark, 1990-1993 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Correspondence with Kaplan and Furth, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Correspondence with Karen Darenbach and Gary Mar, 1979-1997 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Merit letters for pay raise, 1989-1990 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Letter to Monty with contract, 1988 May (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Spring mobilization, 1967 February (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Grounds for Merit raise, undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Concerned Faculty correspondence with Congress, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Set theory, exponentiation theorems, and equivalences (Winter-Spring), 1981 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Unlabeled calculations and proofs, undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Philosophy 32: Lecture notes (Spring), 1997 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Philosophy 31: Textbook (Fall), 1997 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Philosophy 31: Lectures 19-29 (Fall), 1997 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Philosophy 32: Lectures and exams (Spring), 1995 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Philosophy 32: Makeup final for Judy Benton (Spring), 1995 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Philosophy 184A: Class materials (Fall), 1964 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Philosophy 184A: Set Theory, lecture notes, and class materials (Fall), 1963 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Philosophy 240: Set theory and class materials (Fall), 1961 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Philosophy 134: Class materials (Spring), 1991 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Philosophy 32: Infinite models (Spring), 1996 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Philosophy 32: Makeup final for Judy Benton (Spring), 1995 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Philosophy 32: Proofs, Shutte and Simmons supplement (Spring), 1996 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Philosophy 134: Class materials (Spring), 1980 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Philosophy 32: Honors materials, 1994-1996 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Philosophy 31 and 32: Readers (Spring), 1998 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Euclid's proof detailing no maximum prime number (Fall), 1996 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Chapter 5, Section 4, Group 1-2, undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Chapter 5, Section 4, Group 3, undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Chapter 5, Section 4, Group 4, undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Chapter 5, Section 4, Group 1-2, undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Chapter 5, Section 4, Group 3-5, undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Chapter 5, Section 4, Group 6, infinite models, undated (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Chapter 5, Section 5, Group 7, undated (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Philosophy 32: New problems for exams, 1985-1990 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Proofs and comments, undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Correspondence with Joe Dauben on biography of Abraham Robinson, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Final draft of Abraham Robinson's biography by Joe Dauben, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Rough draft of Abraham Robinson's biography by Joe Dauben, undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Recursion with respect to omega in Zermelo set theory, 1975 August (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Philosophy 134: Syllabus, proofs, and readings (Fall), 1982 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Arithmetic for one-to-one functions, 1990 September (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Proof of cancellation law by double induction, undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Philosophy 134: Final exam, 1980 June 11 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- The power of Hartogs' theorem, 1981 March (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Arithmetic of natural numbers (Winter), 1978 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Fourth reading assignment, undated (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Philosophy 134: Class notes, 1975-1976 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Philosophy 134: Lecture notes and assignments, 1976-1978 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Philosophy 134: Class roster (Winter), 1976 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Philosophy 134: Lecture notes (Winter), 1978 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Philosophy 134: Lecture notes (Winter), 1974 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Finite Sets, Dedekind and otherwise, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Unlabeled bundle of concepts, 1974-1982 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Finite set theorems and union of denumerable number of finite sets, 1976 March (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Theory of finite sets and Russellian definition, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Recent work on proof that W x W, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Peano's arithmetic definitions, undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
- "The Hidden History of the Korean War," I.F. Stone, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- "The Great Road," and "The Life and Timed of Chu Teh," by Agnes Smedley, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- The New Emperors, "China in the Era of Mao and Deng," by Harrison E. Salisbury, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Family correspondence and with Bud, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Bar sinister, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Loan to the Peace Movement, 1967-1968 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Financial statements, 1967-1969 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Driving accident, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Lease of Glenn House, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Ad for peace clippings, 1983-1984 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Correspondence with R. Montague, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Ernst Strauss and Ted Forrester memorial, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- "The Radical Liberal Strategy in Action: Arnold Kaufman and the First Teach- In", 1972 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Papers for New Mobilization Committee against the Vietnam War, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Ed Keenan correspondence (Spring), 1984 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- SCITCA: Correspondence with the "sisters", 1986 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Correspondence with various friends (Bill Kunsler, Mitch Goodman, Doug Dodd), 1971 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- 1968 class reunion, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- Bruin ad for Middle Eastern peace, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- Peck, Ring, and McReynolds essays on the future, undated (Box 29, Folder 17)
- Tax protest correspondence with IRS and Elder Manufacturing Company, 1970-1971 (Box 29, Folder 18)
- Black and Brown clippings, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Ellsberg rally rental, Kalish and Gluck (Fall), 1971 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Yorty on Students for Democratic Society and New Left, and Putnam publications, 1968-1969 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Kalish photograph, 1970 April (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Correspondence with Jane Fonda regarding airfare reimbursement, 1970 June 5 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Cambodian crisis and rally, 1970 May 9 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Kalish helps dishonorable discharge, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Newsletter for People's Coalition, 1973 March 22 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Dow Chemical demo, undated (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Actions as chair and Philosophy Department ranking, 1964-1968 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Off-campus talks: Santa Barbara Police Conference, JSL review, 1967-1970 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Anti-war demonstrations, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Declined invitations and interviews, 1968-1969 (Box 30, Folder 13)
- HCIS action against A. Johnson and MOBE response, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 14)
- Correspondence with Bob Adams, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 15)
- Reaction to Kalish's book, 1964-1965 (Box 30, Folder 16)
- Correspondence with Richard on proofs for KM, 1982-1983 (Box 30, Folder 17)
- Correspondence with Harcourt Brace and Richard, 1965-1966 (Box 30, Folder 18)
- Central American fundraiser, Senator Dodd, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 19)
- Gender Studies: King and Eisler, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 20)
- Fairchild termination issue, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 21)
- Letters from colleagues and friends, 1965-1966 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Pre-chairman letters to Kalish, 1957-1964 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Letters to Rolf Eberle, 1965-1966 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Personal correspondence, 1955-1964 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Correspondence from colleagues and friends, 1964-1965 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Correspondence from colleagues and friends, 1966-1967 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Free Speech Movement regulations, YSA sponsor, 1963-1967 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Papers for New England vacation (Fall), 1993 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Political magazines (Sane World, Southern Africa, Middle East Review, and Korea Focus), 1974-1979 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Political newspapers, 1968-1969 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Correspondence related to political activism, 1968-1969 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Political magazines (Rights, Roots, Respond, Bill of Rights Journal), 1972-1980 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Student alienation report, Bruce Compas, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Articles on Lewis Fretz, Santa Monica Corsair, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Philosophy 6A: Notes (Spring), 1947-1948 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Random news clippings, undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Political magazines (Memo, The UAG, Annex Canada), 1973 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Issues of Resistance and fliers on Shah's visit to America, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Community service requests for speakers and interviews, 1969-1980 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Richard Chase Defense Committee, undated (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Philosophy department meeting minutes, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- American Airlines, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Political correspondence and news from activist organizations, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Political newsletters and magazines (PISS), 1970 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Dissertation by Stephanie Edwards-Evans on career guidance at Santa Ana College, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 5-6)
- Clippings, correspondence, and other materials on Vietnam, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Stephanie Edwards-Evans dissertation final copy, undated (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Edwards-Evans dissertation committee notification, 1976 May (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Edwards-Evans dissertation copy for L. Barrister, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Dissertation committee meeting for Edwards-Evans, 1976 June 1 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Copy of original Edwards-Evans dissertation, 1975 November 6 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Revised copy of Edwards-Evans dissertation #2, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Revised copy of Edwards-Evans dissertation #3, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Edwards-Evans dissertation proposal, undated (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Class notes for theory of knowledge (Fall), 1951 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Comments on Edwards-Evans dissertation, 1976 June (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Rough notes on theory of knowledge class at UC Berkeley (Spring), 1948 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Ms. McDonald on sleeping and waking, 1953 September (Box 35, Folder 11)
- "Why Is There More Evidence for Classical Mechanics Than Classical Theology?", undated (Box 36, Folder 1)
- "Prospectus of Research in the Philosophy of Perception," paper by R.M.Yost, undated (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Philosophy 181: Formulation of arguments and bibliographies (Fall), 1951 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Language and metaphysics paper by Kalish, 1953 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Malcom on memory paper by John Turk Saunders (Fall), 1963 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Philosophy 188: Taught by C.D. Broad and notes (Spring), 1954 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Broad and perceptual nominalism paper by Richard Montague, undated (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Theory of perception notes, 1947 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Phenomenalism collection of papers by G.F. Stout, R.I. Aaron, and C.D. Broad, 1938-1939 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Russell, relation of sense data to physics, and ultimate constituents of matter, 1910-1915 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- "On the Nature of Acquaintance" and "Definitions and Methodological Principles," articles by Russell from Monist, 1914 (Box 36, Folder 11)
- "Refutation of Idealism," "Defense of Common Sense," and "Proof of External World," G.E. Moore, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Short papers (Lazerowitz, Berlin, Braithwaite, and Will), undated (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Ayer, basic propostions, undated (Box 36, Folder 14)
- "The Problem of Universals," Kalish on Parmenides, undated (Box 36, Folder 15)
- Papers on epistemolgy by N. Malcom and Russell, undated (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Analysis of perceptual judgments, 1943 (Box 36, Folder 17)
- Mr. Thomas on waking and sleeping, undated (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Notes for epistemology, Professor Marenke, 1943 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- "Dreaming" review by Kalish, undated (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Philosophy 31: Records (Spring), 1973 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Philosophy 31: Records (Winter), 1985 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Philosophy 31: Handouts (Fall), 1978 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Philosophy 250: Basic studies logic, Gary Mar (Winter), 1978 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Philosophy 31: Hambourger (Fall), 1977 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Philosophy 31: Chapter 1, exercises (Spring), 1973 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Philosophy 31: Final exams (Fall), 1974 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Philosophy 31: Final exams (Spring and fall), 1962, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Philosophy 31: Final exams (Spring), 1964 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Philosophy 31: Old exams for quarter system (Summer), 1960 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Philosophy 31: Exams for quarter system (Summer), 1969 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Philosophy 31: Michael Bennet (Summer), 1971 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Philosophy 31: Exams, records, references, and evaluations (Fall), 1972 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Philosophy 31: 16 binary truth functions (Spring), 1973 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Philosophy 31: Exams, quizzes, handouts, Beauregard (Winter), 1972 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Philosophy 31: Exams, quizzes, handouts, Beauregard (Summer), 1972 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Philosophy 31: Lecture notes (Spring), 1973 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Philosophy 31: Old material, Gary Mar (Spring), 1973 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Bennet's system of modadic logic (Fall), 1973 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Philosophy 31: Lott's exam (Fall), 1965 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Philosophy 31: Raymond Van Zuyle's final exam (Fall), 1962 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Philosophy 31: Michael Downing's final exam (Fall), 1972 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Philosophy 31: Lectures (Fall), 1972 (Box 38, Folder 12)
- Philosophy 31: Lectures (Spring), 1978 (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Cooley's rules for natural deduction, undated (Box 38, Folder 14)
- Final exams and answer keys, 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 15)
- Philosophy 31: References (Spring), 1973 (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Philosophy 31: Records (Summer), 1979 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Philosophy 31: Class announcements (Spring), 1979 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Philosophy 31: Single axiomatic material for sentential logic, Gary Mar, undated (Box 39, Folder 3)
  Single Axiomatic Material for Sentential Logic
- Chapter 3 solutions, Andrew, undated (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Philosophy 31: Chapter 3, exercises, 1973 June (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Philosophy 31: Chapter 2 exercises, undated (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Philosophy 31: Chapter 3 exercises, undated (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Philosophy 31: Records (Fall), 1979 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Philosophy 31: Lectures, exams, exercises and solutions (Summer-Fall), 1979 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Philosophy 31: Knight/Knave problems by Allan Nelson and Gary Mar, undated (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Philosophy 31: Records (Fall), 1982 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Philosophy 31: Lectures (Fall), 1982 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Philosophy 31: Lectures and exams (Winter), 1985 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Philosophy 31: Records, student evaluations, and note to Warren Quinn (Spring), 1989 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Philosophy 31: Records, Kaplan, and Chaitin article (Summer), 1988 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Philosophy 31: Lectures and exams (Spring), 1989 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Philosophy 31: Records (Summer), 1989 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Newspaper clippings on People's Park, 1969-1970 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Newspaper clippings for Wednesday Club, Special Senate meeting (Fall), 1968 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Correspondence with David Bolduc, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Letters to Mary Helmstrom, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Philosophy 135: Letters of recommendation (Spring), 1974 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Philosophy M221A: Letters of recommendation (Spring), 1976 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Brent Williams recommendation (Fall), 1977 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Monica Lord recommendation (Fall), 1977 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Curtis Hellenbrand recommendation (Fall), 1977 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Gary Bock recommendation (Fall), 1977 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Eliot Krieger recommendation (Fall), 1979 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Paul Buchberg recommendation, 1979 January (Box 41, Folder 12)
- Diane Wells recommendation, 1978 February (Box 41, Folder 13)
- Mark De Modena recommendation, 1978 January (Box 41, Folder 14)
- Stephen Stillman recommendation, 1977 May (Box 41, Folder 15)
- Mark Emerson recommendation, 1973 June (Box 41, Folder 16)
- Theresa Szeliga recommendation, 1978 March (Box 41, Folder 17)
- Dorit Bar-On recommendation, 1980 October (Box 41, Folder 18)
- Retirement contract, 1975-1979 (Box 41, Folder 19)
- American Association of University Professors (AAUP) bulletin on Angela Davis, 1971 October (Box 41, Folder 20)
- Academic Senate meeting minutes on Angela Davis, 1969 October 30 (Box 41, Folder 21)
- Academic Senate meeting minutes on Angela Davis, 1969 November 11 (Box 41, Folder 22)
- Academic Senate notice of assembly, 1969 November 3 (Box 41, Folder 23)
- Academic Senate meeting minutes, 1969 October 13 (Box 41, Folder 24)
- ACLU, 1968-1969 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- American Committee for the Protection of the Foreign Born (Spring), 1969 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- AAUP meeting on McCarran Act (Spring), 1966 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Committee for the Defense of the Bill of Rights, 1968-1969 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- GI Civil Liberty Defense Committee, 1969 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Jim Hayes Defense Fund (Summer), 1969 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Emergency Civil Liberties Committee, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Congress of Racial Equality, 1967-1969 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- NAACP Legal Defense Fund (Committee 100), 1966-1969 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- Correspondence (Fall), 1972 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Black Youth Conference, undated (Box 42, Folder 11)
- Brown Berets, East LA Free Clinic, 1969 July (Box 42, Folder 12)
- Community Alert Patrol (Spring), 1967 (Box 42, Folder 13)
- "Notes on Free Description Theory," Lambert, Karel, Journal of Philosophical Logic, V. 1, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 14)
- Correspondence, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 15)
- Van Fraassen articles, undated (Box 42, Folder 16)
- Russell on Meinong, undated (Box 42, Folder 17)
- Lambert, Karel, Journal of Philosophical Logic, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 18)
- Tyler Burge, Journal of Philosophy, v. 71, no 7, 1974 April (Box 42, Folder 19)
- Dana Scott's paper "Existence and Description", undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
- "Moving Toward Scott Models", 1974 October (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Scott and Kaplan descriptions, undated (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Scott article on descriptions, undated (Box 43, Folder 4)
- "What is Russell's Theory of Descriptions?" David Kaplan, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Quine: From math, logic, undated (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Quine: Methods and descriptions, undated (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Quine: From methods, existence and singular inference, undated (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Quine: From Math and Logic, theorem vs metatheorem, undated (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Quine: 40 Identity, undated (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Quine: Math and Logic, Sections 4-6, undated (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Quine: From Math and Logic, quasi quotation, undated (Box 43, Folder 12)
- Frege: From On Sense and Nominatum, undated (Box 43, Folder 13)
- Tarski-Semantic conception of truth, undated (Box 43, Folder 14)
- Carnap: Meaning and Necessity, Sections 7-8, undated (Box 43, Folder 15)
- Substitution, undated (Box 43, Folder 16)
- Bondage and Freedom, and rationale of present form, undated (Box 43, Folder 17)
- Counter-instances, infinite domain, and invalid argument, undated (Box 43, Folder 18)
- Metatheorems: Abbreviations, annotations, and reduction of des-cal, undated (Box 43, Folder 19)
- Proof of claim in VII: Invalid argument, relativization, and false translation, undated (Box 43, Folder 20)
- "Completeness Considerations for Variable Binder Calculus", undated (Box 43, Folder 21)
- Operator calculus and completeness, undated (Box 43, Folder 22)
- Various notes on completeness of description calculus, 1979 February (Box 43, Folder 23)
- Henkin on logic of equality, undated (Box 43, Folder 24)
- Leichti's point on fallacy by EI in abbreviated derivations, 1966 January (Box 43, Folder 25)
- Talk for logic colloquium on equivalent formulations, undated (Box 43, Folder 26)
- David K. Lewis materials, 1967-1968 (Box 43, Folder 27)
- Greenberg on logical form, undated (Box 43, Folder 28)
- Philosophy 32: Interesting notes on descriptions, Howard Sobel (Fall), 1965 (Box 43, Folder 29)
- Strawson's semantics and Mates' article, undated (Box 43, Folder 30)
- Comments on Lambert and Tyler, 1972-1974 (Box 43, Folder 31)
- Student records (Spring), 1989 (Box 43, Folder 32)
- Proofs of T420-425, undated (Box 43, Folder 33)
- Xerox notes (Winter), 1987 (Box 43, Folder 34)
- Exams (Spring), 1980 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Concerning a problem in the KM book and description rules, 1976-1978 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Lectures, exams, and homework problems (Fall), 1985 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Philosophy 133: Duplicates of bundles in preparations (Winter), 1987 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Philosophy 133: On descriptions from Principia Mathmatica, undated (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Tax data ann, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- "Is Religion Reasonable?" (Spring), 1958 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- "Anecdotes by Mates About Our Teachers", undated (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Paul Marhenke, 1946-1947 (Box 44, Folder 9)
- From my students and the big cheat (Summer), 1948 (Box 44, Folder 10)
- Photographs and sketches, undated (Box 44, Folder 11)
- "Letters to a Peacenik: Hate and Humor", 1967-1968 (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Correspondence (peacenik), 1966-1969 (Box 44, Folder 13)
- Hiring and unhiring Angela Davis, San Diego presentation, 1970 September (Box 44, Folder 14)
- Correspondence with chair and faculty displacement, 1969-1983 (Box 44, Folder 15)
- The Journal of Philosophy Volume 72, No. 19, 1975 November 6 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Fregean and Russelian problems (Spring), 1982 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Comments, fourth exam, Part II (Spring), 1982 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Philosophy 133: Final exam (Spring), 1982 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Philosophy 133: Comments on exam 5 (Spring), 1982 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Philosophy 133: Comments on exam 5 (Spring), 1982 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Charitable giving and Ann Kalish, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Russellian and Fregean descriptions, Chapter VIII, 1980-1982 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Hamilton High, authority legitimate and illegitimate, 1968 December (Box 45, Folder 9)
- The Sunday Night Club (Arthur Wallach's group), 1968 November (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Reiber Hall (Richard Marriott), 1968 October (Box 45, Folder 11)
- Forum on Paris Peace Talks, 1968 July (Box 45, Folder 12)
- CDC Conference to Dump Humphrey, 1968 June (Box 45, Folder 13)
- Panel discussion on matter of J. Oppenheimer, (Hibbs, Sheridan, Berwick), 1968 June (Box 45, Folder 14)
- Van Nuys High, 1968 June 3 (Box 45, Folder 15)
- Speaking engagements, 1972 February (Box 45, Folder 16)
- Cal State Philosophy Club, 1970 November (Box 45, Folder 17)
- Fraternity houses at UCLA, 1970 October (Box 45, Folder 18)
- Glendale Jr. Chamber of Commerce, 1970 August (Box 45, Folder 19)
- Van Nuys High School (Spring), 1970 (Box 45, Folder 20)
- Kiwanis talk, 1970 May (Box 45, Folder 21)
- Materials on invasion of Cambodia and Angela Davis, 1970 May 1 (Box 45, Folder 22)
- Beverly Hills High talk on Angela Davis and academic freedom, 1970 April 24 (Box 45, Folder 23)
- Loyola Law School, 1969-1970 (Box 45, Folder 24)
- WLA talk, 1970 February (Box 45, Folder 25)
- Loyola University student protest, 1970 January (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Crisis in higher education, 1969-1970 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- UCLA Dental Faculty Club talk (Fall), 1969 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Temple Beth, 1969 (October) (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Beverly Hills Men's Club (Fall), 1969 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- ABC Channel 7, Prospect/Talmadge, M.J. Hooper/Dan Kibbie, 1969 June 30 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Talk on conscientious objection, 1968-1969 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- Talk with five clergy, 1969 March (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Dinner and talk in Glendale, Thomas H. Carver, 1968-1969 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- Teach-in: Unanswered letters (Fall), 1967 (Box 46, Folder 10)
- Teach-in: Expenses and reservations (Fall), 1967 (Box 46, Folder 11)
- Teach-in: Bills, 1966-1967 (Box 46, Folder 12)
- Teach-in: Program (Fall), 1967 (Box 46, Folder 13)
- Teach-in: Titles for talks, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 14)